(Sheldon:)and I'm not in love with you.
(Sheldon:)And psychology has once again
(Sheldon:)proved itself the doofus
of the sciences.
(Penny:)Well, maybe.
(Penny:)But I'm still glad we did it.
(Penny:)I do feel closer to you.
(Sheldon:)And I, you.
(Sheldon:)And yes, that's
how you say that.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, so, given our
newfound intimacy,
(Sheldon:)I'd say we have
(Sheldon:)some hard choices to make.
(Penny:)Like what?
(Sheldon:)Gary Con--
do we fly or drive?
(Sheldon:)Do we wear costumes?
(Sheldon:)And if so...
(Sheldon:)who gets to be Gary?
(Sheldon:)Thank you for walking me home.
(Penny:)I just want to make sure
you get there safe.
(Sheldon:)Well, this is me.
(Sheldon:)It's been a very
interesting evening.
(Penny:)It really has.
ALL: Surprise!
Aah!
And after I let you be Gary!